<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chapter-19-Javascripts on</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/chapter-19-javascript/</link><description>Recent content in Chapter-19-Javascripts on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/chapter-19-javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chapter 19 Programming For the Web</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Chapter-19-Programming-For-the-Web/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Chapter-19-Programming-For-the-Web/</guid><description> Practical-Requirement-4 • explain JavaScript terms and programming techniques
Advantages-of-Separating-JavaScript-Code-File Client-Side-Code Javascripts HTML-Elements</description></item><item><title>Example Of Bad Password</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Example-Of-Bad-Password/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Example-Of-Bad-Password/</guid><description>abc
1234AAA
The abc password is too short and does not meet minimum length
requirements/number of character requirements
Does not meet requirement for different types of characters
Passwords must not be easily guessed and this is a simple pattern
1234AAA password has a sequence of characters/numbers
&amp;hellip;has repeating characters
Neither have a combination of upper/lower case/number/special characters.
#password</description></item><item><title>Javascript</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Javascripts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Javascripts/</guid><description> Loops-in-Javascript Use-Of-Comment-In-Javascript Others/Advantages-of-Separating-JavaScript-Code-File Benefits-Of-Array Others/Primitive-Data-Types Variable-In-Javascript Others/Sample-Code Definitions-Of-Javascript Terms Others/Sample-code-2 Error-correction-in-javascript sample-code-3 Others/Drawback-of-using-switch Others/Consolelog #Javascript</description></item><item><title>Laser Transmission</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Laser-Transmission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Laser-Transmission/</guid><description>Advantage of laser transmission:
Between spacecraft (in orbit through vacuum) To connect sites across roads Provide (temporary) network connection in e.g. disaster areas where cabling is not possible. Disadvantage of Laser Transmission
Short range only in atmosphere due to dispersion of (light) beam by particles in atmosphere Accurate aiming of (light) beam may be more difficult Difficultly in connection is increased if sender / receiver are moving require line of sight.</description></item><item><title>Loops in Javascript</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Loops-in-Javascript/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Loops-in-Javascript/</guid><description>![[Pasted image 210402113954.png]]
Code is embedded within the body HTML code (global) variable (tableout) is declared The HTML table values are placed within the variable First/outer loop (on 4th line of JS code) executes 10 times« «to create 10 rows using global variable and HTML code each row Second/inner loop is executed each time outer loop executes «to create 10 columns/cells First time inner loop executes, the cell contains 1*1=1&amp;hellip; «second time inner loop executes, the cell contains 1*2=2 «third time inner loop executes, the cell contains 1*3=3 «up to cell that contains 1*10=10 When inner loop reaches 10, first row of cells is complete« «next row is started with 21=2, 24 etc.</description></item><item><title>Pilot Implementation</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Pilot-Implementation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Pilot-Implementation/</guid><description>WiFi internet access for guests in a chain of hotels:
Running in one hotel until it is working perfectly When working perfectly it can be installed in the other hotels The method is more effective than installing in all hotels and discovering problems If it does not work only one hotel is affected not the whole chain of hotels Staff at the hotel can be used to train staff at the other hotels Feedback is collected and collating reviews by guests/users in one hotel Will take longer to fully implement all guest access to Wi-Fi in all hotels compared to direct Bank pilot Implementation</description></item><item><title>Practical Requirement 4</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Practical-Requirement-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Practical-Requirement-4/</guid><description>demonstrate a range of object-based programming techniques
recognise data types (including: number, string, Boolean, array, object) assign and understand the term variables carry out calculations and basic string manipulation use arrays use comparison and logical operators use conditional statements (including: if, else, else if, switch) use loops (including: for, for/in, while, do/while) use iterative methods create functions trap errors control events create html forms to interact with the user add comments to explain JavaScript code • output/display data to: HTML documents HTML elements alert boxes the browser console • add interactivity to web pages</description></item><item><title>Type of form input</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Type-of-form-input/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Type-of-form-input/</guid><description>Type Of Form Input:
Buttons that can be clicked to activate a action
Submit button that sends the form to the dataset
Reset button to clear the form so that the customer can start again
Checkboxes but allow multiple choices to be made
…when checked attribute set the switch is ‘on
…only the ‘on’ state is submitted with form</description></item><item><title>Use of Encryption</title><link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Use-of-Encryption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Chapter-19-Javascript/Use-of-Encryption/</guid><description>Uses Of Encryption:
Encryption protects information by scrambling it using an algorithm with an encryption key to create data Data cannot be understood without the key (Asymmetric encryption) uses public keys which can be accessed by anyone so no need to send key to specific user Private key is known only to recipient so no risk of key interception by unauthorised persons Protects data transferred over the internet between web browser and servers reducing possibility of financial data being stolen Secures email messages to prevent confidential data being read by unauthorised persons Protects cloud storage from outside attacks to prevent confidential data being read by unauthorised persons Prevents the theft of data on USB and external drives Used in VPNs for secure data transfer across public networks Prevents use of stolen passwords to protect personal data from use in e.</description></item></channel></rss>